（携帯電話の着信音）
Your bloodstained peace is the real crime.
（久利須(くりす)）
お前たちの血塗られた平和が―
本当の罪なのだ
Kurisu.
（陵駕(しのぎ)）久利須
Theresa.
テレーザ
Don't do this.
（陵駕）もうやめて
You must know you're being used.
自分が利用されているのは
分かっているでしょう？
We both are.
（久利須）それは お互いさまだ
Torri thinks he's brainwashed me.
トーリは
私を洗脳したつもりだろうがな
Auma is dead.
（陵駕）アウマは死んだわよ
I warned him, but you know how he was.
警告したが あいつらしい
You're going about this all wrong.
（陵駕）こんなやり方 間違ってる
I'm a father.
（久利須）俺は父親として―
I have to move time forward,
for my son's sake.
あの子のために
時を進めねばならないんだ
I've gone too far to turn back.
もう後戻りはできない
Take care of Harris... my son.
羽利須(はりす)を 息子を頼む
Wait, Kurisu!
（陵駕）待って 久利須！
（久利須）ぐおおっ
おっ うっ…
（灼(あらた)）うっ うう…
Let me crack the case right now.
（灼）この事件を
速やかに解決します
Meaning?
（雛河(ひなかわ)）というと？
The culprit is Kurisu O'Brien.
犯人は 久利須･オブライエン
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
♪～
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the lost memories that flee
once they're liberated and banished
Are an everlasting cubism.
Cause I know that in a future gone mad,
Even nightmares are peaceful.
RESET, RESET, yeah.
The midnight sun
awakens and turns to a riot.
A gun for a faux-friendly kiss.
A knife for a faux-revolutionary hug.
Get rid of it all, even the frozen chains.
Reality is always outside your head.
In a world seen through bestial eyes,
There is neither darkness nor light.
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the false memories that flash before
your eyes impatiently and impulsively
Are an everlasting cubism.
～♪
"Inspector"...
（炯(けい)）インスペクター
I have to tell Arata.
灼に… 知らせないと
はっ
Maiko!
（炯）舞子(まいこ)！
（舞子）はっ
（うめき声）
Damn you!
（炯）貴様！
Now, who are the Ministry of
Foreign Affairs' undercover investigators?
（トーリ）さあ
外務省の潜入捜査官は誰です？
I don't know!
知らない！
Don't lie to me.
正直になれ
Don't you want to keep
your lovely wife from danger?
美しい奥さんが大変だぞ
Stop!
やめろ！
Let me rephrase the question.
（トーリ）聞き方を変えよう
I have information about your brother.
私は あなたのお兄さんの情報を
知っている
What?
何？
（舞子）はっ
If you talk, I'll tell you.
あなたが話せば教えてあげますよ
I really don't know anything!
本当に何も知らない！
Excuse me, Third.
（梓澤(あずさわ)）ちょっと サード
（トーリ）あ？
What is it?
何ですか？
Let's have a quick chat outside.
（梓澤）少し 外で話そうよ
I swear I'll save you, Maiko!
（炯）必ず 助ける 舞子！
It's only a threat.
（トーリ）ただの脅しですよ
Is that the issue here?
（梓澤）そういう問題か？
Don't take Public Safety for fools.
公安は まぬけじゃない
They'll raid the place any minute now.
強制捜査まで 秒読みだ
So what's the big idea
with taking more hostages?
なのに 人質を増やすとか
何 考えてるの？
I will have them become Eternal White.
彼らには エターナルホワイトに
なってもらいます
If I claim that they converted
and joined Heaven's Leap...
で ヘブンズリープに
入信したということにすれば…
You really think that'll fly?
（梓澤）
それで通用すると思ってるわけか
We have Bifrost on our side.
我々にはビフロストがついている
Very well. I'll leave this to you.
分かった ここは任せるよ
Are you dissatisfied with my efforts?
私のやり方に不満でも？
I'll see my job through to the end.
Don't worry about that.
仕事は最後までやるよ 安心しな
（突き飛ばす音）
（舞子）ううっ
ああっ
ああ…
You're...
（如月(きさらぎ)）あっ あなたは…
Look at this.
（灼）これを見てください
Harris Sho Flannagan
（天馬(てんま)）うん？
久利須の息子は―
Kurisu's son joined Heaven's Leap?
ヘブンズリープ教団に
入信していたのか？
Let me start from the top.
順を追って説明します
First, Torri joined Heaven's Leap.
まず トーリが教団に入信
Then, when the special religious zone
was proposed, Nisei vanished
その後 宗教特区構想の
プロジェクトが発表されると―
仁世(にせい)が姿を消し―
and Kurisu's son ended up
in a vegetative state.
教団にいた久利須の息子は
植物状態に
Then, Kurisu fell ill.
そして 久利須も発病
You're saying Torri is behind everything?
（入江(いりえ)）教祖代行が
全部の裏にいるってのか？
Yes. Torri manipulated Kurisu
into orchestrating these attacks.
（灼）はい トーリが
久利須を操って事件を起こした
But he couldn't count on
Kurisu getting sick, could he?
（天馬）でもよ 病気まで
計算どおりにはならんだろ
On the contrary, I don't believe
the illness was a coincidence.
（灼）むしろ
“偶然 発病”のほうが疑わしい
Shion,
didn't the list of members include...
（雛河）はっ 志恩(しおん)さん
確か 教団名簿に
Yes.
（志恩）ええ
Cancer treatment and artificial cancer
research specialist Dr. Saburo Nihei.
入信者に ガン治療
人工ガンの専門家―
二瓶(にへい)三郎(さぶろう)博士がいる
Meaning Kurisu's illness
was artificially induced,
（灼）つまり
久利須の病気は―
人工的に引き起こされた
in order to control him.
彼を操るために
Wow, Inspector.
You're firing on all cylinders today.
すげえな 監視官
脳細胞フル回転って感じだぜ
So, how do we prove it?
で どう証明する？
We don't have a warrant for a search.
教団への強制捜査の許可は
下りてないぜ
We'll take Kurisu and Shinogi in custody.
久利須と陵駕の身柄を押さえます
Then let's consider negotiating
with Heaven's Leap.
その上で 教団との取り引きも
視野に入れましょう
Negotiate with the mastermind?
主犯と取り引きなんて
I'd do anything
これ以上のテロを防ぎ―
to prevent further attacks
and rescue our infiltration team.
潜入した２人を助けるためなら
何でもしますよ
I'm in, Inspector.
俺は乗ったぜ 監視官
So, how do we catch them?
で どうやって捕まえる？
We use the location data from the drones
used to implant bombs.
爆弾を埋めるのに使った
医療ドローンの位置記録
They automatically access a data bank
when they perform remote surgeries.
遠隔手術の時に―
自動で データバンクに
アクセスする仕様になっています
Got it. I'll check them ASAP.
（志恩）分かった
大至急 調べてみる
Maiko.
（如月）舞子さん
I'm sure you're worried, but...
（如月）不安でしょうが きっと
（舞子）ええ
I know.
They won't kill us
while they still have questions.
相手に聞きたいことが
あるうちは殺されません
It's Kei I'm worried about.
心配なのは 炯のほう
えっ？
Kei could easily kill everyone here,
炯なら ここにいる人たちを
簡単に殺してしまえる
but he's restraining himself.
でも そうしないよう我慢している
We left our home to escape that violence.
そういうことから逃げて
国を出たのに
I suppose you might call it "karma" here.
日本語で
因果応報っていうんでしょうか
We saw so many deaths in our motherland.
母国では 大勢の死を見ました
But we still tried to find peace together.
なのに 私たちだけ
平和になろうとした
In the end,
I lost my eyesight in an explosion,
結局 私は爆撃で視力を失い―
and even in this peaceful country,
Kei still works as a soldier.
炯は この平和な国でも
兵士として働いているのだから
ううっ ああ…
はっ
ああ… はっ
（ドアの開く音）
んっ
Crime Coefficient is 40.
（ドミネーター）犯罪係数 40
Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
執行対象ではありません
トリガーをロックします
I thought I'd find you here,
（灼）会えると思ってました
Sister Shinogi.
シスター陵駕
Inspector, I've found logs
of a transplant on Kurisu.
（雛河）監視官
久利須への移植手術記録を確認
What made you think I would be here?
なぜ 私がいると考えたの？
It's because you're trying to help Kurisu.
あなたは久利須を
助けようとしていますから
I suppose you would've preferred him?
彼だったら よかったのにね
This all began with a plan
事の発端は―
あなたと久利須 アウマ 仁世の
４人が立てた計画だった
devised by you, Kurisu, Auma, and Nisei.
A plan to expose crimes
against immigrants.
入国者への犯罪を告発するために
Yes, that's right.
（陵駕）ええ そのとおりよ
Wasn't Auma smuggling arms?
He was a criminal himself!
アウマこそ
武器密売人の犯罪者じゃねえか
Those weapons are made to break
after being used for a certain period.
あの武器は 一定期間使ったら
壊れるようにできている
Auma was doing it deliberately
in order to control
紛争国での武器流通を
コントロールするため―
the trafficking of weapons
in war-torn countries.
あえて アウマが
やっていたことなんですね？
You provided him with funding.
その資金を あなたが出していた
We were treating symptoms.
（陵駕）対処療法よ
It took time and money,
but it was effective.
お金も時間もかかるけど
効果は あった
Then, you thought of
a more effective method.
そして
もっと効果的な手段を考えた
You would use terrorist bombings
入国者そのものが
排除されないよう―
to eliminate criminals and expose crimes
without having to expel immigrants.
爆弾テロで悪党を排除し―
犯罪を暴露する
We called it the Final Salvation Plan.
私たちは終末救済プランと呼んだわ
It should never have been
put into action.
実行すべきではないプランです
Yes, your father once said the same thing.
（陵駕）そう かつて
あなたのお父さんも―
同じことを言っていた
はっ…
But our plan was used.
だけど 計画は利用された
Used by a power
that exceeded our imagination.
私たちの想像を超える力によって
What power?
それは 何ですか？
Bifrost.
ビフロスト
Believers in the Ministry of Welfare
（トーリ）
厚生省の信者からの情報で―
tell me that we will be raided soon.
もう間もなく
ここに強制捜査が入ります
Heaven's Leap has served its purpose.
（裁園寺(さいおんじ)）教団は
もう十分 役目を果たした
Have the gears accomplish
their final objective.
あなたは歯車に
最後の目的を達成させなさい
Yes, Mom.
はい 母さん
There will be an open seat
in Bifrost soon. A seat for you.
（裁園寺）間もなく
ビフロストの席が １つ空く
あなたの席よ
The rest will work itself out.
そうなれば あとは どうにでもなる
Yes.
（トーリ）はい
You'll succeed to my brother's seat,
which Homura stole.
（裁園寺）
かつて 法斑(ほむら)が奪った兄の席
それをあなたが継ぐの
We will win this game.
このゲーム 必ず 私たちが勝つ
ハァ…
Your brother, you say?
兄 ねえ…
He really is just like his father.
（裁園寺）ホント 父親にそっくり
Time's up.
時間切れよ
Then let me handle the rest.
では あとは お任せを
Suit yourself.
（裁園寺）好きにして
What is it?
（ドクター）どうした？
My shift's not over yet.
（ドクター）
交代の時間は まだのはずだ
（衝突音）
（２人）はっ
（ドアの開く音）
（２人）あっ
（如月）はっ
うっ… ううっ
Maiko, Kisaragi.
舞子 如月
Kei!
（舞子）炯！
（如月）監視官
Inspector!
Dangerous bottoms have escaped.
（トーリ）
危険なボトムが脱走しました
The bottoms have stolen doctors' uniforms
ボトムたちは
ドクターの装束を盗み―
and are holding
a visually impaired woman hostage.
目の不自由な女性を
人質にしています
If you spot them,
report them to the nearest doctor at once.
見つけしだい
近くのドクターに通報を
（炯）チッ
見つけしだい
近くのドクターに通報を
What's the situation, Kei?
どういう状況？　炯
There's a wall ahead.
（炯）壁がある
I think Enforcer Kisaragi can escape
if she uses me as a stepping stool.
俺を踏み台にすれば
如月執行官を―
逃がすことができそうだ
Inspector?
はっ 監視官？
Hurry.
早く行ってください
If you don't escape, we'll all be killed.
あなたが逃げなければ
全員 殺されます
Please wait. I...
待ってください 私は
I'll bring help.
必ず 助けを連れてきます
Please do.
頼む
（深呼吸）
I know Arata will come to save us.
（舞子）必ず あっちゃんが
助けに来てくれる
Yeah.
ああ
はっ
（舞子）はっ
（炯）うっ
Torri!
トーリ
How ill-behaved you bottoms are.
たちの悪いボトムだ
（炯）ううっ
（発射音）
（炯）がっ おっ
Kei!
（舞子）炯！
Take them away.
連れていけ
What is Bifrost?
（灼）ビフロストって何ですか？
A powerful organization that controls
the group called the "foxes."
（陵駕）
狐と呼ばれる集団を統括する―
強大な力を持った組織
It's likely that Torri is involved
with Bifrost as well.
トーリも ビフロストに
関わっている可能性が高い
So they're the mastermind?
そいつが黒幕だってのか？
Probably, but that's all I know.
恐らく でも
これ以上は私も知らない
Please tell me one thing.
１つ教えてください
Why did you have us
take custody of Kurisu's son?
久利須の息子を僕たちに
保護させたのは なぜです？
Because that boy is a weakness
to Theresa and me.
（久利須）あの子は
私とテレーザにとって弱点だからだ
Kurisu.
久利須
My wife passed away
soon after our son was born.
（久利須）息子が生まれて すぐ
妻に先立たれた
After that, Theresa cared for him
as if he were her own son.
それ以来 テレーザが―
我が子のように面倒を見てくれた
She loved him.
愛してくれた
He was such a kind boy. He was our hope.
とても優しい子
私たちの希望だった
He said that he wanted
to improve the plight of immigrants
あの子は 入国者の現状を
改善したいと言って―
and went to join Nisei.
仁世の元に行ったの
But that derailed everything.
だけど それがすべてを狂わせた
It was Torri.
（久利須）トーリだ
This would never have happened
if Nisei were healthy.
仁世さえ無事なら
こうは ならなかった
You swore not salvation, but revenge on
the society that created discrimination.
（灼）あなたは救済ではなく―
差別を生む社会そのものへの
復しゅうを誓った
You really are a chip off the old block.
さすが 慎導(しんどう)篤志(あつし)の息子だ
You can read so deeply into the mind
of someone you've never met.
会ったこともない相手の心を
そこまで読むとは
You brainwashed the bombers
as revenge for your son.
自爆犯は あなたが洗脳した
息子さんへの報復として
You're right.
（久利須）そのとおりだ
I blew the people who abused him
in the name of religion to smithereens.
宗教の名を借りて
あの子を虐待した連中は―
粉々になった
It's highly probable that your cancer
was artificially induced.
（灼）あなたのガンも
人為的なものだった可能性が高い
I know.
知っているさ
I never wished for it,
but it's shown me what I should live for.
望んだ病ではないが―
生きる理由を明確にしてくれた
Stop, Kurisu.
やめて 久利須
That's enough, Theresa.
（久利須）もういい テレーザ
Give Public Safety
what I left in your care.
私が預けたものを
公安局に渡してくれ
It will be my final insurance.
それが最後の保険になる
（銃声）
あっ
あ… ああっ
うっ
（入江）うっ
I'll stop the bleeding.
し… 止血します
You OK, Temma?
大丈夫か？　天(てん)さん
I'm fine. How's the Sister?
心配ねえ シスターは？
（陵駕）ハァ…
Arata Shindo...
慎導 灼…
You...
あなたは…
No! Don't die on me!
ダメだ 死んじゃダメだ！
You mustn't become like us...
私たちや…
あなたのお父さんのようには―
or like your father...
ならないで…
Even if a century were to go by
in this very instant,
（篤志）もしも 100年が―
この一瞬の間に
たったとしても―
it would be no surprise.
何の不思議もないだろう
It's raining.
雨が降っている
This is the truth.
（篤志）これが 真実だ
Arata Shindo, do your job!
（入江）慎導 灼！　仕事をしろ！
（灼）あっ
I'll find the sniper.
俺が スナイパーを捜す
You can't! We don't know
their numbers or positions.
はっ ダメです
敵の数も場所も分からない
Check with drones first...
ドローンで確認してから
Or you'll be shot like Todoroki!
廿六木(とどろき)さんみたいに
撃たれちゃいますよ！
This is what enforcers are for!
（入江）
こういう時のための執行官だろ！
Enforcers are people, not shields!
執行官は盾じゃない 人間だ！
うっ
Target eliminated.
（ジャックドー）
ターゲットは始末した 撤収する
I'm pulling out.
（久利須のせき込み）
（吐血する音）
I'll see you on the other side, Theresa.
向こう側で会おう テレーザ
（携帯電話の着信音）
んっ
I see the pieces are all in place.
（トーリ）準備は整ったようですね
I hope you'll actually
lure the target out this time.
今度こそ 標的を―
誘い出してくれるのだろうな？
Certainly.
（トーリ）間違いなく
Psycho-Pass exceeding permissible values
in Shinmisono, Itabashi.
（アナウンス）板橋(いたばし)区新三園(しんみその)で
規定値超過のサイコパスを計測
Inspectors on duty, proceed to the scene
with Enforcers.
当直監視官は
執行官と急行してください
（志恩）ん？
当直監視官は
執行官と急行してください
Mao!
（志恩）真緒(まお)ちゃん！
Kisaragi!
（灼）如月さん！
（入江）如月！
I'm glad you're safe.
（雛河）無事で よかったです
I'm here, too.
（天馬）俺もいるぞ
（雛河）はっ
あっ…
What, is that all I get?
何だい そのリアクションは
I'm sorry.
（如月）すみません
Don't apologize.
（灼）謝らないでください
Your cover was blown, huh?
潜入が バレたんだな？
Kei's been captured. At this rate...
（灼）炯は捕まってる
このままじゃ…
So has Maiko.
舞子さんも
What did you say?
はっ 今 何て…
Inspector Ignatov and his wife
（如月）
イグナトフ監視官と共に―
are both being held
in the Heaven's Leap facility.
奥さんも教団施設に
拉致監禁されています
（灼）はああ… あ…
Here.
（如月）これを
（２人）んっ
Inspector Ignatov gave me this.
イグナトフ監視官から預かりました
（椅子から立ち上がる音）
（入江）ん？
（足音）
I'll analyze it ASAP.
今すぐ 解析する
Inspector Shindo,
慎導監視官 教団へ強制捜査を
please, search Heaven's Leap.
ぐっ…
The chief's talking to the bureau chief.
課長が局長と話しています
Let's do what we can for now.
我々は
今 できることをやりましょう
（天馬たち）んん…
With all four pocket watches,
（志恩）
懐中時計が４つそろって―
I found the server
used to synchronize their plan.
彼らの計画同期用のサーバーが
見つかった
So, this is the "Final Salvation Plan"
the Sister talked about?
これが シスターが言っていた―
終末救済プランってやつか
It's the plan that Kurisu modified
for these attacks, to be precise.
正確には―
久利須が今回の事件に変換した
計画表です
Look.
（志恩）ねえ
（入江）ん？
There's one unfinished objective.
まだ未達成の目標が １つある
Governor Komiya.
（灼）小宮(こみや)都知事
I see.
そうか 最初の爆破で
殺す予定だった
The first bomb was meant to kill her.
That's why they needed a sixth.
だから ６つ目が必要に
An Immigration Bureau observer
murdering the governor.
入国管理局オブザーバーが
都知事を爆殺
It will be symbolic
of the immigration issue.
入国者問題を
象徴する事件になります
Kurisu plans to take all the blame.
（灼）久利須は
すべての罪を背負うつもりです
This case is so critical, it can't
be closed until the culprit is dead.
これだけの事件―
犯人が死ななきゃ終わらない
（呼び出し音）
（灼）うう…
都知事につながらない！
I can't get through to the governor!
Why would Heaven's Leap
want the governor dead, anyway?
（入江）大体
教団が何で都知事を？
The special immigrant zone's
been on the table since her predecessor,
移民特区は 前の都知事の時から
構想はありましたし―
so it would go through anyway.
どの道 成立するのに
The governor's death
would create a power vacuum.
（灼）都知事がいなくなれば―
権力の空白が生じる
And they'll reap all the benefits?
その隙に 教団が利益を独占？
But they'll be raided sooner or later.
でも 遅かれ早かれ 強制捜査は入る
They can't last any longer.
教団は限界だ
Any power they get
won't make a difference.
権力を手に入れても意味がない
Maybe Torri assumed
we wouldn't press them this hard?
トーリの想定では―
ここまで追い詰められるはずでは
なかったとか
Even so, he could have stopped the plan
at any time.
だとしても
計画は いつでも中止できた
Kurisu's ultimate goal is to expose
the society that produces discrimination.
久利須の最終目標は
差別を生む社会そのものへの告発
Then what is Torri's?
なら トーリは？
What if he never cared
about the special zone?
もしかしたら―
特区は どうでもよかったのかも
What?
（入江）はあ？
If the governor dies, he'll gain
something better than the special zone.
都知事が死ねば
トーリは特区以上の何かを得る
But I don't know what that something is!
その何かが 分からない！
We can't do anything about that, can we?
分からないのは しかたないんじゃ
Putting the big picture together
when we have missing pieces
何かが欠けた状態で
全体像の完全な推理は―
is impossible, isn't it?
不可能じゃないかと
I see.
そうか
That piece...
それが―
is Bifrost.
ビフロスト
（リンク中の音）
Risk analysis is complete.
（細呂木(ほそろぎ)）リスク計算が終了した
Do it.
やりたまえ
Yes, ma'am.
（霜月(しもつき)）はい
I have something I want to confirm, too.
こちらも確認したい点が出てきた
Which is?
（霜月）というと？
A string of killings
without malice aforethought.
（細呂木）殺意なき殺人の連鎖
Methods designed
to outwit the Sibyl System
シビュラシステムの裏を
かくようなやり方が―
have grown exceedingly objectionable.
極めて不愉快になってきた
ということだ
（一同）ん？
（二瓶）んっ
（炯）ふんっ！
（二瓶）うおっ うっ
（二瓶たちのうめき声）
（発射音）
（炯）ぐがっ
うおっ
（炯）ううっ あ… はっ
ん？
はっ
You're with the MOFA
Suppressing Action Department!
お前は… 外務省行動課
I can't believe I'm saving you twice.
（宜野座(ぎのざ)）
二度も助けることになるとはな
Don't give us trouble.
世話を焼かせるな
（ドアの開く音）
Our status?
（宜野座）首尾は？
We have Nisei. I hid him in a safe place.
（須郷(すごう)）仁世を確保
安全な場所に隠しました
Hey, what's going on?
（炯）おい どういうことだ？
We're investigating, like you.
お前と同じく 捜査だ
They're holding my wife captive.
妻が監禁されてる
Do you know where?
場所を知らないか？
はっ
There's a hidden passage
in Torri's office.
教祖代行の執務室に
隠し通路がある
Try there.
恐らく…
I can't thank you enough.
恩に着る
Hey.
（宜野座）おい
Should we really be leaving Torri to him?
（須郷）いいんですか？
教祖代行を任せて
He'll be fine.
大丈夫だろう
（通信機の着信音）
Oh, it's you!
（カリナ）あら
Governor!
都知事！　やっとつながった！
I finally got through!
You sound awfully intense, Mr. Detective.
（カリナ）刑事さん
すごいけんまくね
You're the next target
of the terrorist bombings.
例の爆弾テロ
次の標的は あなただ！
（カリナ）あっ
If you know that, then arrest the culprit.
分かってるなら 犯人を逮捕して
Are you at the special religious zone
press event venue?
（灼）そこは 信仰特区ＰＲの
イベント会場ですか？
We're on our way there.
（オワニー）向かってる最中です
Location data confirmed.
（灼）位置情報を確認
引き返してください
Please turn back.
We can't.
（オワニー）無理です
Immigrants are already receiving
harsher treatment due to these incidents.
ただでさえ事件のせいで―
入国者に対する風当たりが
強くなっているのに―
We can't afford to cancel.
中止などできません
（カリナ）ハァ…
Is it worth more than your life?
（灼）命より大事ですか それ！
I'm the governor.
This is something only I can do.
（カリナ）私は都知事です
私にしかできない役目があるの
You're so stubborn!
ううっ この 分からず屋！
なっ！
Listen. In that case...
（灼）いいですか それなら…
（通信機の着信音）
（灼）うっ
Hang on, I'm getting a call.
キャッチです ちょっと待ってて
Who do you think you-
（カリナ）あなた 何 その…
Inspector, it's finally time.
（霜月）監視官 ようやくよ
For the raid?
（灼）強制捜査！
Yes. I'll head to Heaven's Leap
headquarters with Unit Two.
（霜月）ええ 私は二係と
ヘブンズリープの本部へ向かう
You stop the terrorist bombings.
あなたは爆弾テロを
必ず止めなさい
Yes, ma'am. The enemy is likely
heavily armed, so be careful.
（灼）了解
敵は重武装の可能性が高いので
お気をつけて
Who do you think you're talking to?
（霜月）誰に向かって―
そんな口利いてるの！
（通話が切れる音）
Governor!
（灼）都知事！
フンッ 分からず屋で
すみませんね
Sorry I'm so stubborn.
What are you talking about?
（灼）何の話ですか もう
Why, you...
この…
Well, in that case,
we'll go with plan B.
（灼）とにかく
それなら プランＢです
What?
ああ？
They're forming a wall
of adherents with clear Hues.
（坂東(ばんどう)）色相がクリアな信者たちで
壁を作っています
A blatant play for time.
露骨な時間稼ぎね
I judge it to be a malicious obstruction
and authorize tear-gas use.
悪質な妨害と判断し
催涙弾の使用を許可します
（信者たちの悲鳴）
（携帯電話の呼び出し音）
Help me, First.
（通話がつながる音）
（トーリ）ファースト
手伝ってくれ
I can't contact Mom for some reason.
なぜか 母さんと
連絡がつかないんだ
Well, you see...
（梓澤）そりゃねえ…
Ms. Saionji has to protect herself, too.
裁園寺さんも
自分の身を守らなきゃいけない
She left me to cover
for your carelessness.
君の不始末のカバーを俺が任された
That's why I have your card.
そのために 君のカードを持ってる
I wasn't told of this!
聞いてないぞ
Try to pull through.
（梓澤）うまく切り抜けろ
If you, as religious as you are,
have total faith in yourself and Sibyl,
君が宗教家として―
自分とシビュラを
信じ抜けたなら―
your Psycho-Pass will remain clear.
君のサイコパスは
クリアなままだ
Damn him...
（トーリ）あいつ…
（携帯電話の呼び出し音）
（通話がつながる音）
This is Third Inspector Torri Aschenbach.
サード･インスペクターの
トーリ･アッシェンバッハです
Have you made up your mind at last?
（代銀(しろがね)）
ようやく 決心がついたかね
Yes. I will become a congressman.
ええ 僕は
コングレスマンになる
But I won't take the seat
that Mom chose for me.
でも それは―
母さんが
決めた席じゃない
Client data secured.
顧客データを確保
There are a lot of names we don't have.
我々が把握していない名前が
かなり あります
Good.
Public Safety's started their search.
よし 公安局の強制捜査も始まった
そろそろ 潮時だ
It's time we left.
（須郷）あっ
Her again?
（宜野座）また あいつか
（銃声）
（久利須）なっ…
（ジャックドー）んっ
Sniper located!
（入江）狙撃手を発見
こっちは任せろ
Leave this to m...!
うっ はっ
Crap.
クソッ！
うっ
How were you able to get here so soon?
なぜ これほど早く到着できた？
Our colleague who escaped Heaven's Leap HQ
教団本部から脱出した仲間が―
found Nisei's pocket watch for us.
仁世教祖の懐中時計を
手に入れてくれたんです
So, this too is God's will.
これも 神のおぼし召しか
I don't mind dying with a detective
instead of the governor.
都知事ではなく 刑事と心中でも
私はかまわない
Target's threat assessment updated.
（ドミネーター）
対象の脅威判定が更新されました
Explosives. Destroy Decomposer.
爆発物 デストロイ･デコンポーザー
Don't move, Kurisu!
動くな 久利須！
はっ あっ…
Crime Coefficient is 45.
（ドミネーター）
犯罪係数 45 刑事課登録監視官
Registered CID inspector.
Warning.
警告 執行官による反逆行為は―
Rebellion by enforcers will be recorded
and reported to headquarters.
記録の上 本部に報告されます
Don't shoot!
（灼）撃たないで
He's dangerous. Please move!
（雛河）
危険です どいてください！
（灼）ううっ つっ…
Target's threat assessment updated.
（ドミネーター）
対象の脅威判定が更新されました
Crime Coefficient is 27.
犯罪係数 27
Not a target for enforcement action.
執行対象ではありません
えっ…
You've committed crimes,
but only because you were being used.
（灼）あなたは犯罪を犯した
でも それは利用されたからだ
I was able to steel my resolve
because they made me sick.
病気にさせられたおかげで
覚悟ができた
I'm grateful to Torri for that.
その点では
トーリに感謝している
You don't have to die here.
（灼）ここで死ぬ必要なんかない
No, this is what I must do.
（久利須）いや こうすべきだ
As the culprit in this case.
事件の犯人として
My anguish led me to my crime.
悩んだ末 犯罪者になった
As a member of the Immigration Bureau...
入国管理局の人間として…
ぐおっ
（吐血する音）
（久利須）うっ おおっ
（久利須のうめき声）
At last,
これで―
I can move time forward.
時を進めることができる
If I don't, this country's problems
will never be solved.
さもなくば この国の問題は―
永遠に解決しない
No, it will never even realize
いや 問題があることすら―
that its problems exist.
気づかないだろう
Moving time forward like this
won't make anyone happy.
こんなことで時間を進めても
誰も幸せになれない うっ
Target's threat assessment updated.
（ドミネーター）
対象の脅威判定が更新されました
Crime Coefficient is 7.
犯罪係数 ７
（雛河）ああ…
ううっ ハァ ハァ… はっ
If my son ever wakes up,
息子が もし 目覚めた時―
I want him to see a beautiful world...
世界が きれいに見えるように
（うめき声）
（吐血する音）
（久利須）う うっ ぐおおっ
This isn't for your son.
（灼）子供のためじゃない
You gave in to evil in order
あなたは
自分の思いを果たすために―
to fulfill your own desires.
悪を受け入れたんだ
くっ ううっ…
God will forgive everything.
神はすべてを許す
Your Psycho-Pass is special.
（篤志）お前のサイコパスは特別だ
Crime Coefficient is 0.
（ドミネーター）犯罪係数 ０
（雛河）えっ？
The trigger will be locked.
トリガーをロックします
（雛河）ああ…
You...
あなたは―
haven't forgiven anyone, have you?
誰も許さなかったじゃないか
（雛河）はっ
Inspector!
監視官！
（信者たちの悲鳴）
Prioritize locating Inspector Ignatov.
（霜月）最優先で
イグナトフ監視官を捜して
Yes, ma'am.
（坂東）了解
（炯の荒い息）
はっ
Maiko!
舞子
（舞子の荒い息）
We're done here, Vixen. Get out.
（梓澤）ヴィクスン
ここは終わりだ 逃げて
But...
（ヴィクスン）しかし
You want another shot at the old Unit One,
right? I'll give you a chance soon.
（梓澤）昔の一係へ
リベンジしたいんでしょ？
チャンスは すぐ作るよ
Understood.
了解
Wait!
（須郷）待て！
Damn!
（宜野座）しまった！
（トーリと舞子の荒い息）
Heaven's Leap is through.
教団も終わりだ いいさ
That's fine.
I'm going to be a congressman, anyway.
どうせ
僕はコングレスマンになるんだ
（２人の荒い息）
Stop right there!
（炯）そこまでだ！
（トーリ）あっ
Kei!
炯！
Maiko!
（炯）舞子！
You don't know when to quit!
（トーリ）お前 しつこいな！
Just leave me alone!
もう放っておいてくれよ！
You keep trailing after me like a shadow.
影みたいに いつまでも
ついてきやがって！
Give up!
（炯）もう諦めろ！
Give up? Me?
僕に諦めろ？
I'm nothing like any of you.
お前らと僕とは
何もかも違うんだよ！
The god we call Sibyl has chosen me!
シビュラという神が
僕を選んだんだから！
Stop! If you're going
to shoot anyone, shoot me!
やめろ！　撃つなら俺を撃て！
（トーリ）ハッ ハハハハッ
Is that your pure and true conjugal love?
清く正しい夫婦愛
ってやつか？　それ
Why not show your true colors?
本性を出したらどうだ！
If you can't say it, I will.
言えないなら 僕が言ってやる
Both of you
お前らはな―
just want to hide your own weaknesses
from each other!
互いに自分の弱さを
隠したいだけなんだよ！
"Love" is just a word you use to justify
愛なんてものは―
己のウソを正当化するための―
your own lies!
言葉でしかないんだ！
The weak must die!
弱者は―
死ね！
ぐあっ ぐっ うっ
ひっ
Dear...
あなた…
I'm sorry.
（炯）すまない
I'm glad you're all right.
無事で よかった
Can you see?
見えてるのか？
I can see your face.
あなたの顔… 見えるわ
（炯）ああ…
You're crying.
あなた 泣いてる
Kei...
炯…
（灼）うっ
（雛河）あっ
（炯）ううっ
Why did Maiko get dragged into this?
何で 舞子が巻き込まれた！
Say something!
何とか言え！
I won't make excuses.
言い訳は しない
You...!
このっ
ううっ クソ！
Damn it!
That's enough.
（霜月）そこまでよ
Get some counseling
and psychological care.
あなたも カウンセリングと
メンタルケアを受けなさい
Yes, ma'am.
はい
We lost another inspector,
（代銀）またしても
インスペクターを失ったが―
but the Relation turned out well enough.
リレーションの成果としては
上々だな
Results confirmed. Apportioning dividends.
（ラウンドロビン）
リゾルツ確認 配当を実行
That was close for you, Shirogane,
代銀さんも
危ないところだったけど―
but this is the end for Homura.
これで 法斑さんは終わりね
But first...
（代銀）その前に
ん？
I have information
リレーション中に死亡した―
supplied by Third Inspector Torri,
who passed away during the Relation.
サード･インスペクターの
トーリ君から 情報提供がある
Indictment
ううっ
As you know, he was Kyoko's son.
知ってのとおり
彼は莢子(きょうこ)さんの息子だ
They behaved in a manner
unbefitting of our game.
２人は ゲームにあるまじき
振る舞いをした
You tricked him, didn't you, Shirogane?
代銀… あの子を たぶらかしたわね
Mom,
（トーリ）母さん
はっ
you must be shocked right about now.
今頃 驚いてるだろうね
This can't be!
（裁園寺）愚かな
Mr. Shirogane revealed the truth to me.
（トーリ）僕は代銀さんから
真実を知らされた
I can hardly believe that my father
was your own brother.
まさか 自分の父親が
母さんの兄だったなんてね
It's your fault my Hue clouded, isn't it?
僕の色相が濁ったのは
あなたのせいなんだね
I'm not the one who needs purification.
真に浄化されるべきは―
僕じゃなく あなただ
It's you.
As of today, the Saionji seat is mine.
裁園寺の席には
今日から僕が座る
Goodbye,
さよなら
Mom.
母さん
Excess interference and assistance
during the game can't be overlooked.
ゲーム中の過剰な干渉と援助
看過できんよ
You bastard! I'll kill you!
貴様 殺してやる！
うぐっ ううっ うう…
You dug your own grave.
墓穴を掘ったのは君だ
Go join your family.
家族の元に行くといい
Review complete.
（ラウンドロビン）審査終了
After collating this data with data
supplied by the First Inspector,
ただいまのデータと―
先ほど提出された ファースト･
インスペクターのデータを照合
eight counts have been found factual.
８項目が事実と断定
You will be stripped of congressman status
and face enforcement.
コングレスマン 資格剥奪の上
執行します
（裁園寺の叫び声）
So, it's just you and me left.
（代銀）さて 残るは
君と私だけだね よろしく
It's a pleasure.
The pleasure is mine.
（静火(しずか)）こちらこそ
By the way,
ところで君は―
you manipulated me to dispose of Saionji,
didn't you?
私に裁園寺を始末させるよう
誘導したろ？
That was a good play.
いい手だったよ
Whatever do you mean?
（静火）さあ 何のことでしょう？
フフッ
We'll take custody of Nisei
and of Kurisu O'Brien's son.
（宜野座）仁世教祖と
久利須･オブライエンの息子は―
うちで保護する
Public Safety would probably
just institutionalize them.
（須郷）公安局が確保しても
施設に送るだけでしょうから
Nisei was collaborating with the MOFA?
仁世は外務省の協力者だったのね
I always knew
you were quick on the uptake.
さすが 頭の回転が速いな
Give Frederica Hanashiro a message:
花城(はなしろ)フレデリカに伝えておいて
"I will humiliate you.
あんたに必ず屈辱を与える
I'm going to make you crawl at my feet."
私の足元に
はいつくばらせてやるって
No way.
嫌です そんな
Tell her yourself.
自分で伝えてくれ
（２人）フッ
Well, that's rude!
何よ もう！
National Center for Medical Research
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
What are you apologizing for?
（炯）何で舞子が謝る？
My Hue clouded.
（舞子）色相が濁っちゃって
Hues have recovered with treatment before.
施設で色相が回復した例もある
Even murder won't necessarily
raise your Crime Coefficient.
状況によっては 殺人でも
犯罪係数は上昇しない
Like for inspectors
and Defense Force soldiers.
監視官や国防軍の兵士と同じで
I'm sorry, Kei.
ごめんね 炯
Don't worry.
安心しろ しっかり
メンタルケアを行えば大丈夫だ
You'll be fine with psychological care.
Sibyl took us in. We must believe in it.
俺たちを迎え入れてくれた
シビュラを信じよう
So, did I get shot for nothing?
何か？
俺は撃たれ損だったってか？
We defended the governor.
都知事を守った
We exposed Heaven's Leap's
illegal activities.
ヘブンズリープの違法な行為も摘発
It wasn't for nothing.
意味は ありましたよ
Hey, Inspector,
（入江）なあ 監視官
you did good.
You don't need to beat yourself up.
あんたは よくやった
自分を責める必要はない
Yeah. Thank you.
はい ありがとうございます
Chief Shimotsuki Mika
You have 1 new message
Regarding Psycho-Pass decline
during pursuit of bomber
はあ？
は… ああ…
Recorded value: 00.00
はあああ？
Criminally asymptomatic?
免罪体質…
Now they know Arata Shindo is criminally
asymptomatic. Does that disappoint you?
（細呂木）慎導 灼の免罪体質が
周知のこととなるのは―
君が望まない展開かな？
There's a reason Sibyl made him
an inspector in spite of that.
（朱(あかね)）シビュラには それでも
彼を監視官に起用した理由がある
So I'm sure he will remain an inspector.
だから 引き続き
彼は監視官のままでしょ？
He's the ideal person for the job.
我々にとって 最も有効な人材だ
Only someone capable of joining Sibyl
can remedy Sibyl's blind spots.
シビュラの盲点を
埋められるのは―
シビュラの一員になれるものだけ
"Once the hares are dead,
the hounds are expendable."
狡兎(こうと) 死して 走狗(そうく) 烹(に)らる
ふむ
I won't let you sacrifice anyone.
誰も使い捨てには させない
They will reach the truth on their own.
必ず 彼らは 自分たちの力で
真実に たどりつく
♪～
Stupid perfection in your own castle
How smart. You cause me to yawn
Look,
The key to the door is in your hand
Don't you let anyone take control
What do you want?
Go get it. Play by your own rule
The winner always controls the game
You stand in your belief
There's no promising future
Always helpless
Crying for the moon
Finger trembles in fear
With the weight of the trigger
There's a way for us
Show them how we fight
Pull the trigger
～♪
（足音）
Sorry I called you over.
（如月）
お呼び立てして すいません
I don't mind.
（炯）別に かまわない
I wanted to thank you as well.
俺も君に礼を言いたかった
You really saved me in this case.
Thank you.
今回の件では本当に助かった
ありがとう
No, I only did my duty.
いえ 私は
自分の職務を遂行しただけです
ん？
May I confess my sins to you?
あの…
罪を告白してもいいですか？
"Psycho-Pass" refers to the measurement
of a person's mind and personality.
This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance
to real persons or groups is coincidental.